advertising-support.com 2014-06-25

# Advertising Support

_Last Updated: November 20th, 2013_

Thank you for using our browser extension (the "Plugin"). The Plugin is owned and licensed to you by Engaging Apps ("we", "us" or "our"). Downloading and installing the Plugin will result in the display of various types of advertising, which is how we are able to make the Plugin available to you for free. As you use the Plugin, we want you to be clear how we're collecting and using your information and the ways in which you can protect your privacy.

This Privacy Policy applies to information collected through the Plugin, as well as other information you choose to provide to us; however, it does not apply to information collected from our employees, contractors or vendors. Specifically, our Privacy Policy explains:

  * What information we collect and why we collect it
  * How we use that information
  * The choices we offer regarding your privacy

We've tried to keep it as simple as possible, but if you're not familiar with terms like cookies, unique identifiers and in-text advertising, then read about these key terms first. Your privacy matters to us, so if you have any questions please contact us. 

Because of the way our Plugin works, certain information may be collected by it but not be accessible to us (or may be accessible only to our service providers who help us power the Plugin). Certain other information may be collected and stored by the Plugin and intermittently accessible to us when the Plugin communicates with our systems. For the sake of simplicity, this Privacy Policy covers all information collected by the Plugin and treats it as information to which we or our service providers may have access, even though in many cases such access is limited or currently non-existent.

1\. **_Consent_**

By downloading or using the Plugin, you consent to this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with this Privacy Policy, you must uninstall the Plugin, which you can do going to Add/Remove Programs in your Control Panel, selecting the Plugin and clicking Uninstall. (Please be aware that disabling the Plugin in your browser settings may not permanently uninstall it.)

2\. **_Advertising Features of the Plugin_**

As mentioned above, the Plugin is supported by third-party advertising, and when you download the Plugin you will see various types of advertisements displayed through your browser as you visit locations on the Internet. You should familiarize yourself with these types of advertising, which are features of the Plugin and are listed below.

The Plugin currently displays several basic types of advertising: (1) sponsored links, (2) traditional display advertisements, such as banner ads, "pop-unders" and interstitial ads, (3) coupons, and (4) video targeted ads. The sponsored links may sometimes appear as in-text advertising. Sponsored links may also be displayed in response to keyword searches you enter through Google, Bing and other search engines.

Before you install the Plugin, we disclose to you on the installation screen that installation will result in the display of advertising. When you expressly consent to the installation of the Plugin (following this disclosure), you consent to receive all types of advertising displayed through the Plugin. Your consent is important so that we can provide the Plugin to you free of charge.

3\. **_Personal Information and Sensitive Information_**

We do NOT knowingly collect personal information through the Plugin. However, it is it is possible that, in very limited and rare circumstances, personal information could be collected incidentally without our knowledge in each case (for example, the Plugin collects the URL's of the websites you visit and in certain cases collects the search terms you enter into a search engine, and so if a URL you visit or search term you enter includes the name of an individual, this name would be collected by us). By the same token, we do not knowingly collect sensitive information.

4\. **_What Information Do We Collect?_**

We collect the domain and the URL of each website visited by you when the Plugin is activated, as well as information about errors. We also collect web log information (which may include unique identifiers we create) as well as other information about the state, city and country in which you are located (but not precise geographic location) and certain generic information like the time you first loaded or activated the Plugin and the type or version of Plugin you are using. Some of this information is collected and stored by cookies placed on your computer by us or our third-party service providers, like our ad server company. For specific information about how we and our service providers use cookies and what information is collected and stored by these cookies, please read the section below entitled "Cookies and Automatic Information Gathering Technologies". When the search features of the Plugin are enabled and you perform a search, the search terms you enter are also collected, along with your IP address and other web log information as described below.

Also, when we display in-text advertising, the technical process we use involves the temporary collection of portions of the content on the web page we are visiting. However, in order to avoid collecting your personal information or sensitive information, we only collect information about web page content when you visit unsecured (i.e., unencrypted) websites, such as user forums; we do NOT do this when you visit secure sites like banking sites where your personal information is likely to be entered or displayed. In any case, when we collect web page content in connection with our in-text advertising, we store this information for only a fraction of a second and do not use it to find out personal information about you or build a profile of your online browsing activity.

5\. **_Cookies and Automatic Information Gathering Technologies._**

We use cookies, beacons and other automatic information gathering technologies to collect web log and technical information and to store your preferences on your computer or other device. Cookies and other strings of characters can serve as unique identifiers. 

The cookies used with the Plugin may include both traditional cookies and "flash cookies." Flash cookies provide a different type of storage on your computer than traditional cookies. The cookies used by us and our service providers store or may be associated with your IP address, the last URL you visited, other technical or generic information such as the date and time you first used the Plugin, your city, state and country (but not your precise geographic location), whether you have clicked on a particular link before, and your decision to opt out of receiving certain types of advertising. We do not use, or allow others to use, cookies (or other automatic information gathering technologies) to collect or store personal information or sensitive information.

Cookies can be prevented by activating the facility that is available in most web browsers that enables the user to deny or accept cookies. Recognize, however, that if you prevent cookies, the Plugin may not function properly. You should also be aware that flash cookies are sometimes more difficult to disable than traditional cookies; however, you can do so following the instructions available here.

6\. **_How Do We Use the Information We Collect?_**

The data we and our service providers collect, including information collected by or associated with cookies, is primarily used to determine which type of advertising to display based on the website you are currently visiting (say, sponsored links or banner advertising) and which advertisements in particular to display; deliver the ads and manage the ad delivery process (including limiting the frequency with which ads can be displayed and honoring your opt-out choices); and determine compensation under our arrangements with advertising partners and other companies. For example, some websites you visit are not eligible for the display of coupons, so URL or domain data may be used to select the proper type of advertising to display. To give another example, we will not deliver advertising when you visit certain websites, and therefore we sometimes use URL or domain data to turn off the display of ads.

We may use some of the web log information we collect, including unique identifiers, to help us get a better understanding of our overall user base (for example, to determine how many of our users use Internet Explorer, how many are Mac users, etc.) and the web domains they access, as well as how many active users of the Plugin there are on a given date. We may also use this information for other internal purposes, such as to help us diagnose problems, to perform research, reporting and analysis aimed at improving our Plugin and other technologies, to manage our systems, and to evaluate the performance of our relationships with other companies. However, we also do not use cookies or web log information for purposes of finding out personal information about you, tracking your browsing history across multiple sites, or building a profile of your behavior for ad targeting or sharing with third-party marketers.

We are always looking for ways to improve our products. To that end, we periodically collect and analyze how you interact with our software and the websites you visit, such interactions with our software features, files downloaded, and advertisements viewed or clicked on. This type of information is collected in the aggregate, and while an IP address or unique identifier may be collected as part of the same process, we do not link this address or identifier to your browsing or purchasing activity for tracking purposes. Web log information, including your IP address, may also be collected and stored by our service providers and marketing partners so that the may improve their own products and services. We do require that our service providers and marketing partners not to use or disclose such information in any way that is inconsistent with this Privacy Policy.

You should be aware that when you click on ads displayed through the Plugin or submit information to an advertiser or other third-party marketer, that third party may collect your information for online behavioral advertising. Some of our advertisers may drop cookies used for online behavioral advertising on your computer when you interact with their ads. You can learn more about online behavioral advertising, and can opt out of online behavioral advertising by certain companies, if you visit http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices.

All of this may sound complicated, but the thing you should keep in mind is that none of the information collected by the Plugin is associated with an individual user, and none of this information is used to identify a particular individual for the purpose of tracking or profiling a user's Internet browsing activity. Remember that we will ONLY use your information in the way we specified when it was collected (including as described in this Privacy Policy), unless we obtain your express consent to different uses.

7\. **_Disclosure of Your Information_**

We will only disclose your information as specifically described in this Privacy Policy. If we want to disclose it differently, we will obtain your express consent before the disclosure.

We disclose information we collect about you to third parties (such as our corporate affiliates, advertisers, coupon providers and partners who bundle and distribute our Plugin) as reasonably necessary to display our various types of advertising and to track the performance of our relationships with these third parties, determine compensation and manage our respective business relationships. We may also share web log information with third-party marketers so that they can target ads to you based on a single domain or search term request (but not your overall browsing history). Finally, we disclose information to service providers engaged to perform other functions on our behalf (such as providing data storage, hosting, ad serving, content distribution, marketing of our Plugin and other products, auditing, and web analytics). We require these third parties to follow privacy restrictions consistent with this Privacy Policy with respect to information we share about you. Since we do not knowingly collect personal information, we do not share it with third parties for their own direct marketing purposes.

We may also disclose your information, anonymously aggregated with information about other users of our products and services, to our clients, business partners, merchants, advertisers, investors, potential buyers and other third parties if we deem such disclosure, in our sole discretion, to have sound business reasons or justifications. For example, when a third party bundles our Plugin with its own downloadable application and distributes the bundled applications together, we may share with the third party the total number of installations of the Plugin our systems have recorded.

We may also disclose your information to third parties when we believe, in good faith and in our sole discretion, that such disclosure is reasonably necessary to (a) enforce or apply the end-user license or other terms and conditions for the Plugin, including investigation of any potential violations, (b) comply with legal or regulatory requirements or a governmental request, (c) protect the rights, property or safety of us, our users or other third parties, (d) prevent a crime or protect national security, or (e) detect, prevent or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues. Finally, if we are involved in a merger, acquisition or asset sale, or in the unlikely event of a bankruptcy, liquidation or receivership of our business, we will provide affected users notice through the www.advertising-support.com website or the Plugin at least thirty (30) days before your information becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

8\. **_Accessing Your Information; Transparency and Choice_**

People have different privacy concerns. Our goal is to be clear about what information we collect so that you can make meaningful choices about how it is used.

As mentioned above, we do not knowingly collect personal information or sensitive information. If you believe that we have inadvertently collected any Personal Information or sensitive information about you, please contact us, and we will try to locate and delete this information. We may ask you to identify yourself and the information requested to be accessed or deleted before processing such requests, and we may decline to process requests that are unreasonably repetitive or systematic, require disproportionate technical effort, jeopardize the privacy of others, or would be extremely impractical (for instance, requests concerning information residing on backups), or for which access is not otherwise required. In any case, where we provide information access and deletion, we will perform this service free of charge, except if doing so would require a disproportionate effort.

Some Plugin users find they do not want in-text advertising, and you can opt out of this Plugin feature by clicking here. If you would like to opt out of your web log information being shared with third parties for their own ad targeting purposes, please click here. In addition, you can stop all advertising through the Plugin if you uninstall it by following the instructions in Section 1 ("Consent") above. 

Please note that even if you uninstall the Plugin (or request the deletion of personal information that was inadvertently collected) information that does not personally identify you and is not stored in a manner that associates it with you may be retained indefinitely. Furthermore, even if you request that we delete inadvertently collected Personal Information, we may need to retain certain information for a limited period of time to satisfy our legal, audit and/or dispute resolution requirements.

9\. **_Third Party Links, Sites and Applications_**

Please note that the Plugin may provide links to third party sites. For example, when you click on an advertisement displayed through the Plugin, you are taken to a web page which is not owned or controlled by us. Additionally, a feature of the Plugin may offer you a menu of third-party software applications which you may download if you choose to do so. Also, third parties who bundle our Plugin with their own Plugins or other software applications may collect end-user data through their own separately-installed applications and not through the Plugin. We are not responsible for the privacy policies, practices or the content of websites, web pages, or applications owned by others, and their collection of information from you is not governed by this Privacy Policy. Accordingly, we encourage you to review the privacy policies and terms of service of those sites and applications when you visit them and before installing any applications so that you understand how they collect, use and share your information.

10\. **_International Users_**

By installing and using the Plugin and providing us with your information, you acknowledge and agree that due to the international dimension of the Plugin we may use the data collected in the course of our relationship for the purposes identified in this Privacy Policy, including the transmission of information outside your resident jurisdiction. In addition, please understand that such information may be stored on servers located in the United States. The data protection and privacy laws of the United States and other countries might not be as comprehensive as those in your country. By installing and using the Plugin, you consent to the transfer of your information to the United States, and you further agree that all transactions relating to the Plugin or our website shall be deemed to have occurred in the United States.

11\. **_Children_**

We do not authorize users under 13 years of age to use the Plugin. If we learn that we have inadvertently collected personal information from a child under the age of 13, we will delete that data from our systems.

12\. **_Information Security_**

We utilize reasonable information security measures to safeguard your Information. For example, we utilize Secure Socket Layer (SSL) encryption technology when data is transmitted over the Internet, and have installed firewalls to help prevent external access into our network. Unfortunately, however, no data transmission over the Internet and no method of data storage can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your information, we cannot guarantee its security.

While we do not seek to collect personal information, when we collect information that is associated with unique identifier, we restrict access to it to our employees, contractors, service providers and agents who need to know that information in order to operate, develop or improve our Plugin. These individuals are bound by confidentiality obligations and may be subject to discipline, including termination and criminal prosecution, if they fail to meet these obligations.

13\. **_Changes to this Policy_**

Our Privacy Policy may change from time to time. We will not materially reduce your rights under this Privacy Policy without your express consent. We will post any privacy policy changes on www.advertising-support.com/privacy.php or notify you about them through the Plugin and, if the changes are significant, we will provide a prominent notice (such as an alert through the Plugin). We will also keep prior versions of this Privacy Policy in an archive for your review. You can always check the "Last Updated" date at the top of our Privacy Policy to see when it was last changed, and we encourage you to check it at www.advertising-support.com/privacy.php from time to time. 

14\. **_Questions_**

To ask questions about our Privacy Policy or to lodge a complaint, contact us by clicking here.
